<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<extension id="textboxfield" status="released" xmlns="http://symphony-cms.com/schemas/extension/1.0">
	<name>Text Box</name>
	<description>The Text Box field is a replacement for both the standard text input and textarea fields. It combines both to create a field that supports text formatting and validation rules.</description>
	<repo type="github">https://github.com/rowan-lewis/textboxfield</repo>
	<url type="discuss">http://symphony-cms.com/discuss/thread/387/</url>
	<types>
		<type>Field Types</type>
	</types>
	<authors>
		<author>
			<name github="rowan-lewis" symphony="buzzomatic">Rowan Lewis</name>
			<website>http://nbsp.io</website>
		</author>
	</authors>
	<releases>
		<release version="2.3.3" date="2013-07-09" min="2.3.2">
			- Add class to the filter prefixes on the DSE for Symphony 2.3.3 compatibility
			- Add Polish translation. Thanks @idea07
		</release>
		<release version="2.3.2" date="2013-06-04" min="2.3.2">
			- Add support for `ImportableField` and `ExportableField` interfaces
			- Fix grouping output for field. Thanks @PascalPiche
			- Improve localisation. Thanks @jurajkapsz
		</release>
		<release version="2.3.1" date="2013-02-03" min="2.3">
			- General cleanup of Field to align closer with the core implementations.
			- Added Italian translation.
			- Fix character limiter feature, now with better UTF-8 support.
			- Add 'None' when the Textbox field is the first display column and the entry has no data so the entry link is created.
		</release>
		<release version="2.3" date="2012-06-02" min="2.3">
			- General maintenance for Symphony 2.3.
			- Added German translation.
			- Fixed issue where text formatter was causing corrupt handles.
			- Sorting is now done on `handle`, rather than `value` for a speed boost.
			- Fix empty elements appearing in the XML.
		</release>
		<release version="2.2" date="2011-04-11" min="2.2" max="2.2.5">
			- Fixed incorrect setting name for `column_length`.
			- Fixed issue causing JavaScript to be executed on the wrong page.
			- Don't rely on MySQL to create tables with the MyISAM, do it ourself.
		</release>
		<release version="2.1" date="2010-11-01" min="2.1">
			- Added checkbox to wrap output in CDATA regardless of formatting.
			- Added checkbox to toggle inclusion of handles in output.
			- Output values instead of handles as parameters if handles are disabled.
			- Fixed datasource filter editor JavaScript.
			- A couple of other minor issues.
		</release>
		<release version="2.0.14" date="2010-02-19">
			- Improved upgrade process.
			- Added a setting that lets you display more than 75 characters in publish table columns.
		</release>
		<release version="2.0.11" date="2009-12-09">
			- Really fixed the upgrade issues, *really!*
			- Changed the way handles are created to make sure they are always unique.
		</release>
		<release version="2.0.10" date="2009-12-01">
			- Fixed issue where upgrades for 2.0.9 where not being applied due to a Symphony bug.
		</release>
		<release version="2.0.9" date="2009-12-01">
			- Added a fancy interface to select filter modes when editing data sources.
			- Added ability to limit input to a specified length.
			- Fixed a few minor bugs.
		</release>
		<release version="2.0.6" date="2009-07-24">
			- Added 'raw' output mode to get unformatted data.
			- Added delegates to modify the publish panel.
		</release>
		<release version="2.0.4" date="2009-06-20">
			- Fixed a couple of minor issues with data sanitisation.
			- Added `starts-with`, `ends-with` and `contains` filter methods.
		</release>
		<release version="2.0.2" date="2009-05-11">
			- This is a complete rewrite of the old extension, it isn't backwards compatible, so don't try to upgrade.
		</release>
	</releases>
</extension>